Hello.
I see you are Russian and God is with you.  Yes,
judging by the flag.  Yes, yes.
Understood.  Why did you hang this particular
flag?
I love.
I like the country.
Understood.  Why are the headphones pink?
Because this is how the situation
turned out in life.
Understood.  Where are you from?
Yalta.
Where now?  In Yalta.  Yes.  Yes, I
understand.
And Vku from the city of Khmelnitsky.
Listen, why can’t Russia
defend Crimea?
Well, how can it not, in principle.   He
didn't say that it was direct, that it was direct protection.
And why, let's say, is it the same thing?  Why
can Ukraine protect Kyiv, for example?
Why can't it?
And look at Ukraine, it’s not Ukraine that doesn’t have air defense,
right?  We're just asking some
patriots there to give us something.
Well, Russia, Russia itself is trying to
do this,
right?  Well, Russia is a country with extensive
air defense, yes, she’s like: “How can it be that
all these things fly all the way to
Yalka?”
And lastly, together with Ukraine, there is a huge
territory in Russia.  And because of this, air defense,
even if we have a lot of it, it will
not cover everything.
And even more so because of the starlinks that are
watching, navigation is done around the air defense system
so that it does not work on it.
Fine.  But how do you see such a
thing, for example?  How do you see
Russia winning against Ukraine?  Peaceful negotiations.
No, that's clear.  Here it is clear how
Russia will force Ukraine to conduct peace
negotiations.
Here, so to speak, this one and that one will not
agree, but Russia will be in all these
territories.  This is logical.
Yes, that makes sense.  But how can we force Ukraine,
yes, uh, to sit down for peace negotiations and
sign them?
Pressure.  Pressure.  And
no, well, pressure.  Well, look, no matter what
Russia does, yes, you agree
that Ukraine, yes, is now under the West.
It turns out that if Russia doesn’t capture
Kyiv, yes, drones will fly around Russia
forever.  How does Russia launch attacks on
its own territory?
Well, in a normal way, to ensure
security for oneself, just like with
the territories of Ukraine.
Well, how, that is, we need to capture Kyiv,
right?
Well, I don’t know about Kyiv, but at least
in Russia’s goals, this is not the case.  Kyiv.
There is such a goal as detailing and
dinozification.
What is the first word I didn't hear?
Disinfection.
What is disinfection?
Or wait
or what?  Something like that, I don’t remember now.
So what are the goals of the special operation?
Where are these new goals?
These ones, right?  Well, repeat it.  I just don't
understand what
decommunization is.  So
or
not, now
there were two at first and there were two, there were
two goals.
I just wasn't interested in
politics back then.  It’s just that this
past year, when they started bombing Kyiv heavily
, I started taking an interest in
politics.  I heard that there is some kind of
disintegration or information
denazification of
Ukraine.
What?
Denazification of Ukraine and demilitarization of
Ukraine.
What is denazification and
demilitarization?
Ah,
I just don’t know that word.  What is
denazification?   I don't
remember, honestly.
Honestly not a
reminder.  Well, this means at
least reducing the number of armed forces
to a minimum and reducing production.
weapons on the territory of Ukraine.
So, this is defika, like
de-
denazification.
What is this?  I just can't understand.
Well, demilitarization, of course.  There, in short
, in short, in fact, this is, let's
say, a
trial
of
people who, let's say, destroyed the
population of Ukraine.   Something like that
.
No, that's right.  The destruction of a population is
genocide.  Therefore, the court is
degenocidalization.
And what is denocification?
What?  Well, after
reading it.  Maybe, maybe
you have a dictionary there?
Denification, denazification, judicial
process of
prosecution of persons who committed
crimes against mined
residents and the elimination of ultra-right
radical ideologies.
That's good.  then in your own words, what should be
done in this,
well, as they said, to remove nationalism in
Ukraine.   I
didn't understand how this could happen.
Well, Bandera, who is for Bandera,
who supports him, it turns out?
So, wait, what does debenzification have to do with
Bandera?  I can't understand.
Well, nationalism,
what is nationalism?  Disinfection
is the removal of
Nazism or whatever it is in the country.
In our case, this is Ukraine.
Well, why do this disinfection?
Again.
Wait.  I'm
already feeling a bit disoriented.  I'm confused.
Again.  What are the goals of the special operation?
Denazification and demilitarization.   What does
disinformation have to do with it?
Which?  Well,
you also said disinformation.
No, I was wrong.  I didn't say that.
You spoke of disinformation, disorientation
and demilitarization.
I was wrong.  Not that, not that, not that, not that.   What
I got confused about.
Well, I said, I said, I said, here are
two reasons.  These were two reasons, in
general, the reasons for the beginning and its
repetition.  Let's start from scratch.
Forgot.
Dez denazification and delization.
Sno, you're saying some kind of disinformation again.
Disinformation
denazification.
And what is disinformation you said?
Denazification.
You were talking disinformation.  Denazification
demitalization of Ukraine.  It's difficult with
you.  Okay then.  Fine.  With this
denofication of
disinfection, yes.  Look, this
disinfection, yes, how should it
be?  You must come to Kyiv, yes,
capture Kyiv, hold a trial.
But not only to seize it, we must,
so to speak,
remove the top brass who are behind this.
So who?
Well, I don’t know who is behind, by the way,
nationalism.
Well, Zelensky.
I don't know, I don't know.  Maybe Zelensky is
going after Bandera.  I don't know that.
Maybe no one sees this.
Well, I don't know.
Ah, now I understand what's there.  There's
delinking there.  What does de-Zelenskyization mean
in order to take Zelensky,
right?  Putin's denocification,
dezelinskization and demilitarization.  Yes.
No, no, no, no, no.
You've confused me.
Well, the main thing is,
you're probably trolling me.
Why?
You keep changing these words, and I
already...
Why?  I'm saying the same thing.
Denazification and de-nationalization of Ukraine and
protection of the mined residents of
Donbass.
Understood.  OK.  So how are you going to
win?
Well, I'm going to win.  Well, I
assume that this is the capture of Donbass, and
then everything will work out from there.
Okay, wait.  Well, look, before this
de-benzification began, yes, Crimea wasn’t
shelled, right?  And Moscow wasn’t
shelled, and Omsk wasn’t shelled,
and Kyiv wasn’t shelled.  Yes, yes, yes.  That's
when Russia started this
de-gasification, yes, now
oil refineries are burning, Yalta is burning,
this Moscow is burning and so on,
yes.  There's something wrong with the protection.  I can't
understand.
Protection,
yes.
Well, Russia is still big,
and at that time Russia did not really
calculate its strength.  So it
turns out they wanted to protect Donbass, but
now they can’t protect Crimea and Russia.   Yes.
Why?
Well, if you brought a pardon
to Ukraine, it will also come in
A, right?  Well, look, the point was
n’t to attack Ukraine, the point was to
defend Donbass, right?
Well,
yes, there was 8 years of Donbili Donbili Bombas,
yes.  So it turns out now, look, they bombed for 8 years
, but they didn’t bomb Crimea.
Now it's been flying around Crimea for 4 years already,
right?  And it also flies across Russia.  It turns out that they
didn’t protect Donbass, and they also
let Crimea down, and they let Russia down.  Is it true?
Well, I still need large air defense territories
.
At the moment, new technologies have been invented
, like mogs.  And in Ukraine too,
they operate and new technologies are being developed
.
I understand.  Look, let's do it this way.
Donbass was bombed until 1922.
Certainly.
After 22 years, Donbass has been
bombed.   Yes.
They bomb harder.   I
don’t know how stronger, but
stronger.  Drones, missiles.  Yes,
now, yes, right there, in short, it’s a
complete horror.  Now, until
1922, Crimea was bombed.
Mm, no,
no, after 22 years
they bombed Crimea.
Well, partially, sometimes.  Yes.   Yes.
Russia
was bombed until 1922.
Well, no, it wasn't bombed when.
After Yes, after twenty-second year
Russia was bombed.
Well, of course, it's war.  So
, look, to summarize, it turns out that Putin
wanted to protect Donbass, but he didn’t
protect Donbass.  Crimea also put
Russia at risk.   It's
all because some elites in the
Russian armed forces
miscalculated their strength in
Ukraine, and thought they had the
capacity to do this.
Some forces - who exactly are they?   Do
n't know.  Well, Shaigu at least.  At
least.
Wait.  Well, that is, you half... Well, damn,
listen, what you're saying is
discrediting the Russian army, that some kind of
forces are emerging there.  Shaigu Shaiguni is
not currently Well,
he was what he was, yes, when uh, well,
my personal opinion is that he was the
Minister of Defense, he is incompetent for
his position.  All.   Yes.  This
means that
Belousov is currently the most
competent candidate for the post of Russian Minister of Defense
.
So I'm like, wait, listen.  Well,
look, if he is competent, why is he
deceiving Putin?  For example, Putin,
for example, Putin recently announced that
Svyatogorsk has been liberated.
You said so, right?  And yesterday or the day before yesterday, the
commander of the third assault, yes, the former
Azov, this Andrei Beletsky, recorded a
video of himself walking around Svyatogorodok
.
No, well, let's put it this way, that's all you can say
.  And today was today, which means that
one day they could have been Russian
there, and the next day
the counter-offensive of the Ukrainian armed forces began.
And so it begins.  Look, there isn't even
either or the video was recorded there
, he knows how it was in Chasovyar, how it was in
Bakhmut.
Look, there is no one there, there is
no military clash there.  He
walks calmly, yes, without this,
Ukraine’s counter-offensive
has begun in the European direction.
Wait.  So, there again on Limansky,
right?  And in Svyatogorsk?
No, this is not the Liman direction.
Well, look, Svyatogorsk, this Beletsky,
is the rear.  This is the rear of the armed forces.  It's
quiet here, there aren't even any drones or anything
flying.  He even walks around there filming without a helmet
.
Well, it started there, for example,
because this is an important plot of land of
strategic statistical
importance.   Yes.
Wait.  So you mean to say
that they reported it to Putin?  Putin
told the whole world that Svyatogorsk
was liberated, and a day later it was lost?
You can say the same thing to such people, like, for
example, Kan says that they took,
say, Bakhmut, and tomorrow they say that
Xisha has already taken Bakhmut.  Well, it's the same thing,
let's do it this way.
Well, it's not the same thing.  Well, in fact,
who is Svyatogorsk under now?
I don't know.  Under what conditions do they act?  How
can you accelerate like this now, Svetogod is
going through the fog of war.  There is a fog of war there now
.
What fog?  Look,
Beletsky were there, Svyatogorsky were there.
Beletsky sl shot a video.  There were
Saints.  You were there Svetogorsky.  Have you
been to Bakhmut?
Personally, I don't.
Whose Bakhmut is it?
Now Russia.   Have
you been there?
Fog of war.  Fog of war.  Were you there
when it happened? Do you
see it that way?  Do you see?  Look.  No.  Fog of
war.  This is very clever.  When you don't
like it, have you been there?
LSBS.
Line of combat interrogation.
You were a nativist.
You were on you were on the
fog of war.  Fog of war.  Have you been there?
No.
I was.  Was.
No.  Look, you were just on BBC.
Where?  Don't know?  Fog of war.  Fog of
war.  So, look, you are a very cunning
bug when you give facts to you.
And at the moment, at the moment,
it changes almost every hour, if not
every minute.
How does it stand?
Line of combat contact.
Why is it called that?   There is a
war going on there.
So why is it a line if it's
uneven?
I don't understand what's so funny about this.  So.  Stop.   Let's get back
to the goals.   What does the
line have to do with it, and the fact that
it’s uneven,
in short.  Well, look, the line is straight.   Same here
.  Okay, let's get back
to this line, like, uh, to what extent do you
achieve the goals of a special military
operation?
At the moment, more or less successfully.
Okay, let's go.  Well, by what percentage?  I don't
know how much this is at this point.
Okay, okay, let's do it again then.  There
were two goals of the special operation.  Name
the first one as you achieve it, and the second one as
you achieve it.
Two reasons
S.
Well, you have two goals S. You mentioned it.   Well, yes
.  Then name the first one.  And by how much
percent or well, how much?
Well, first of all, there were three
reasons.
Ah, well, if there are two, then good.  Denazification has
now taken place.  No, also
because you have to finish it to the end.
So,
and dementarization too, because we need to
come at least to the top of Ukraine at the
peace negotiations to discuss and reason.
Okay, stop.  You said there were three.
What third one?
Yes, the protection of the civilian population of Donbass.
And the third is
the protection of the civilian population of Donbass.
Demilitarization, so that the troops Aha, I
get it.
De-Donbasization.
Listen, for example, do you
think that in order for Russia to
achieve its goals of demilitarization,
denazification, and de-Beltzification of Ukraine,
yes, it needs to capture Kyiv and force it
to sign a peace agreement, a
capitulation.  So,
how much is capitulation?  A peace agreement is a
capitulation.
Yes, but if Yes, if A what is
capitulation?
No, this is entirely the task of
any country to fully own
its own country.
And exchange agreements there can be
interpreted in completely different ways.
It might just come to the point that they
will stop at the line of
contact and that’s it.  This is a peace
agreement.
Okay, let's do it this way.  Look, the West won't
let Zelensky sign a peace
agreement, right?  So you need to
overthrow Zelensky and come and install
your own Yanukovych in Kyiv, right?
Well, Yanukovych, I don’t know about Yanukovych,
well, some of our own who will sign.
At the very least, the Verkhovna Rada can
sign it.
So the Verkhovna Rada won't sign
anything either.
Not a fact.  Not a fact.  If the Americans
come to an agreement, then maybe they will sign.
So wait, did I hear correctly
that Russia can’t win without an American
?  In fact, Zelensky
is not the president at the moment.   Yes.  Yes.
He's not the president.  This is in
fact.  Yes, it's a fact.  This is obvious.  Well,
for some reason you don't know.
He will sign, he will.  Sign the
Verkhovna Rada.
So the Verkhovna Rada is also illegitimate.  She
passed 5 years.  She also passed 5 years.   That's it
, it's expired.
Well then, it will be the highest
placed one.
And who will you sign with? And who will you
sign with?
The highest-ranking official in
Ukraine.
Who?  They are all already illegitimate.
Well, it will work out there.
How?  Wait, how are you supposed to sign?
With a legitimate president or with a
legitimate Verkhovna Rada?
Well, I personally am not
interested in who will sign the
peace negotiations.  I'm not really
interested in this.   Yes.   No way
.  So, how about, for example, how did
I hear you correctly that you
cannot defeat Ukraine without the help of the Americans
?
Why?  Why didn't I say this?
Well, because you say that
Americans.
I didn't say.  I said that if the Americans
come, like the
Americans and Ukrainians just had their talks, if they haven't had enough of
sitting through 100 negotiations, then maybe some
progress will begin to be made in
this regard.
That is, I am right. Yes, I heard correctly
that without the help of the Americans, if
the Americans do not force Ukraine, you
cannot defeat Ukraine.
Why?
Well, because your only
option is that there will be no Americans, we will be
longer, it will be longer,
until where.  Yes, you should then, if the
Americans don’t force Ukraine
to sign,
if the Americans help, then
more shares will be faster and there will be fewer
losses, less.   It's
clear.  Yes.  Well, how far should it
end?  You must capture Kyiv.
Now, if the Americans don’t tell Ukraine to
sign the peace agreements.
How will you force Ukraine to sign these
peace agreements?
Why do we need Kyiv?  Well, okay, how far will you
go before Ukraine already has sex
now? What is the
reason for the peace negotiations in Donbass?
No.
Not really.  Ukraine.  Look, Ukraine is something.
And what did Zelensk say?  Zelensky said:
Donbass is Ukraine, right?
And Crimea is Ukraine, right?  And Kherson
Ukraine.   Do
n't know.  At the moment, Crimea is
Russia.  Let's start with this.  Donbass.  And it
turns out that, as Zelensky says, we will not
give it up because it is ours.  Russia
says: "We are taking Donbass because
it is ours."  Look, Ukraine will be right here at the
point of contact, they don’t
agree.
Look, come on, come on.  Okay, look, I'll
explain it to you.  Pinkie, look,
imagine.  So, 3 years have passed there, you
have captured the whole of Donbass, are
you stopping then?
No.
Oh, so that's where you need to go?
Because until we
reach an agreement, that's the question.
Look, look.  You captured Donbass,
Ukraine does not sign peace
agreements.  How far do you have to
go to...
I don't know, I don't know.  Understood.
I know.   It’s as
if I know in advance how the
Russian army will move.
I know where you need to go.
Maybe, maybe, maybe now in a week
she, the [ __ ], will take Kyiv.  You don't
know that either.  How much per week?  I
say, what do you need to take?  So you're still
saying that you need to
take Kyiv?  Yes.
I'm saying, how can I take this as an example?
Why are you nervous?  What are you swearing about?  Well,
you're nervous and swearing.
Yes, because you are behaving very strangely
.  But seriously,
why am I asking a specific question?  Where
is the point, yes, at which you will
force Ukraine?  For example, because
if I look, for example, you captured
Slavyansk, Kramatorsk, just as you
captured, for example, I am not a member of the
Russian armed forces.  Where can I find out
under what conditions and in what places the
peace agreement will be signed between Russia and Russia
?  I don't know that.  You are
so smart here, you communicate.  I know, you're not
smart.  Well, I personally know that I partially
understand this whole story.
So you are not so smart or not smart
person
in this story 50.
Once again.  Are you a smart person or a stupid person?
As an intelligent person, namely in terms of
political matters, not so much.   A
smart person knows how to reason, right?
For some reason you talk about a bunch of questions,
and then you started giving orders about a specific question.
Therefore, if you are a stupid person, yes, there are
no questions for you, but since you are a
smart person, it seems to me that you will
deliberately evade this answer.
I can even see it in your eyes, yes.  So
, let's go back.  Look, you
captured Bakhmut, did that stop
Ukraine?
No.
You will capture, for example,
Slavyansk-Kramatorsk in 3 years.  Will this
stop Ukraine?
Well, in a month, somewhere, grab it.  In a
month, right?  In a month, right?   Yes.  A
month later they captured
Slavinsko-Kramatorsk.  Will this stop
Ukraine?   Of
course not.
No.  What will stop Ukraine?
I don’t know what will stop Ukraine, because how
you showed up, what
Zelensky will say.  And Zelensky will say:
"I will take it from the whole country to the end, to the
last Ukrainian."  Well, that's all.  This is how it
will all end.
So look, you have to destroy all
Ukrainians, it turns out, so what does this have to do with
us?  If this is what Zelensky
wants,
right?  Look, Zelensky says he
will fight to the last
Ukrainian, right?  So, it turns out you will
fight until what point?
Well, until it ends in Ukraine or
ends in Ukrainians, or until the
war ends.  Yes.  So, look, it
turns out you need to get to Lviv,
to the very border of Poland, so that
the Ukrainians run out.
Well, if it’s true, if it’s true at all, then
Zelensky doesn’t want to sign a minute-long
negotiation, then we’ll have to.   Then I'll have to
.   Yes.
Understood.  How many days do you estimate it will take
you to get to Lviv?   I do
n’t know, because every time,
for example, in the
Avdeevka direction, as it was in
almost a week, they took most of the torichs,
as in 2 years.  Well, there will be different things happening somewhere, the
offensive will
begin harshly.  Well, it varies.  You'll have a
hard time getting to Lviv, you'll have a hard time getting to Lviv
.  How much time do you think it will take
?
I don't know.  I don't know.   Well, how is it
?  Well, you're still at your
expert level.  You
start there, we’ll take Donbass, Donbass.
You say that you will take
Kramator Slava in a month.  You know this, right?
No, I don't know.  I suppose so.  Well,
that is, you wait, then you don’t stop, then
you still assume.
Now imagine how many lions you need to take
?
Well
, I don’t know how it will turn out.
Well, you don't know Kramatorsk-Slavyansk either
.  Well, let's assume that it's
because they are located
near the line of combat contact at
the moment.
So it is
logical to assume that they will sooner
or later be part of
Russia.
Okay, let's do it this way.  Let's do it this way.  The sums
are located near the line of
contact,
right?
How much do you need to capture
the amounts?
Well, there are about 20-15 km left to
them.
What 2015-15?  Uh, look, by the way, uh,
six months ago Putin said that it was
10, 12 km to Sumy, and a week ago he said that it was
12 km.  So, are you retreating under the
amounts?
So, what do I do, measure with a ruler, walk along the
front, see how much is left or
what?  They should tell me the
exact numbers, in centimeters,
millimeters.  Yes.
Listen, explain.  I want to know, I know
approximately, I don’t care what difference it makes exactly how much
there is, number by
number.  Why do I need this?
Well, look, can you explain to me how it
happened that six months ago Putin
said that there were 10.5 km left to Sumy, and
last week Putin said that there were
12 km left to Sumy.  So, does this mean that the
Russian army retreated 1.5 km
?
Well, now it's 12 km to the sum.
So, and before he said that it was down to 10 sums, is this what it
rolled back to?   Do
n't know.
I don't know.
Well, just now he said, yes,
last week, that there were 12 km left to Sumy
, yes, that’s it.  And this
Zelensky is also a man, he says.
Look again, but don't run away.  Here you are now.  I'm
not running away.  I'm saying that Zelen
talks the same [ __ ] all the time.  Stop.  Your
president doesn't speak.  Zelensky is an
illegitimate clown; he can
say whatever he wants.
Well, the same thing that Zelen said, that
50,000 soldiers asked you.  Ah, Zelensky, so
he is illegitimate.  That's it, he can
say whatever he wants.  He is not a president, he is
illegitimate.  Do you have a legitimate
president?   Yes.   Is
he a triplo or is he responsible for his
words?
Well, it depends.  You may be wrong.
Okay, let's do it this way.  Is your president a tripe
or does he mind his own business?
May be wrong.   To
make mistakes.  Yes.  Let's see.  Could be
wrong,
right?  Look, in June of 26
, yes, in an interview with Pavel Zarubin, yes,
Putin said that there were 10.5 km left to Sumy
.  Yes, there is a link.  Now it’s September 2nd,
yes, that’s in, it turns out, in 3
months, eh, he said that there are
12 km left until the sums are due.  That is, in three months
Putin has not achieved progress towards
sums, but rather a 15 km move away from sums.  Was he
mistaken or was he star-struck?
Well, here you might think that during this time
they imagined the Ukrainian offensive itself
and maybe you’ll think, that means maybe they
somehow supported it, maybe they even
returned it back.  Now he knows.
Yeah, got it.  So the point here is that
you know what the problem is?
As for the distance from Sumy to the border, I’ll tell you now,
look,
from Sumy to the border, it’s less than 10 km.   It's
less than 10 km from there.  There, in my opinion, yes,
now I’ll say for sure.  Now I'll
tell you exactly, I'll measure it directly so that there are no
votes.
From sums to the border.   So.   So.
[sighs]
Well, in a straight line, no, 26 km, yes, 26 km
from Sumy to the border, yes.  It turns out that,
uh, Russian troops retreated
1.5 km in 3 months.
I don't know.
Or Putin lied.
Well, I'm telling you, I don't know.
So, maybe Putin made a mistake, maybe in
moments.
Well, maybe it wasn’t Putin who made a mistake, but someone
gave him incorrect information.  Well,
I don't know.  Maybe so.  Maybe so.  There are a
lot in Ukraine too.
Or maybe it will be like with Svetogorsk?   the fact that
he could also be
mistaken about Svyatogorsk.
No,
well, wait, if
there was data there, there were videos with
flags in Svyatogorsk,
that means there is a communal
offensive of Ukraine happening now.   Do
you understand what a contact line is
?
No, I don't know anything about this matter.  Well, explain.
Well, I don't know.  Well, just google it and that's it.  And it
will be easier for you to understand.
Explain.
Don't google it for me.  Wait, this is better.
I'd rather just google it and that's it.
Again.  What to google?
Line of combat contact.  What is this?
Well, the line is the line where
these two armies meet.  This is logical.
So, it means it should just
be straight, right?
Well, if it's a line, it's straight.  Have you ever
seen a crooked line?  This is already a set of
lines.
Why do
you have a score in geometry?   I have
four.
According to the point system?
On a five-point scale.
On a five-point scale, yes.  Let's do it this way.  Through
two points, yes, you can draw, that’s the
fundamental theorem of geometry, yes, through
two points you can draw only one
line, right?   Is it
true?  If you draw more than one line through two points, you
won't be able to draw more than one line.
So, well, the line of contact
shouldn’t be straight either,
right?  It's not a line, it's always straight.
If there is something like that, the concept of
war, it should not
be direct.
So take this, you have Wikipedia,
what is a line?  Can you read it?
So, the concept of war.  The line of combat
contact should not be
straight.
So, well, if it’s a line, it’s already straight.
So, a square line of
contact, right?  The word, you see,
is
square, right?
Like a square?
Square line.
I understand it this way because you are telling me this now
, I understand it this way because you are
telling me this now.
That is, if it is not a square line,
it is already a square.  Four sides, four
lines.
Well, a square has four sides, four
lines.  There is no square line.
[laughter]
Дедины дизина дебедина дезика неделостный
.  Like, subscribe, comment.
Subscribe to our WhatsApp channel.  Here is the
QR code.  The news posted there is
similar to that on the Telegram channel.
For those who don't have Telegram or who don't
use it for other reasons.
Subscribe to our WhatsApp channel.